thirdsector.co.uk 2019-11-18

# Privacy Notice - Haymarket

Last updated: 25th March 2019.

## Introduction

Haymarket Media Group Limited respects and is committed to protecting your privacy. We aim to maintain consistently high standards in our use and storage of your personal data, and endeavour to comply with the Data Protection Act 2018, the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and other relevant legislation.

To reflect changes in privacy laws, this updated Privacy Notice aims to clearly inform you of how we use your personal data, how we ensure it is kept secure and your choices about its use. We hope this can help you to make informed decisions when using our websites or other services we provide.

In this Notice, references to “we”, “us” and “our” refer to Haymarket Media Group Limited. Personal data, as defined by the GDPR, means any information which relates to a living individual who can be identified, either directly or indirectly, from this information. For example your name, email address, postal address, telephone number and other personal details.

From time to time we will update this Privacy Notice, so encourage you to refer back to this page regularly. If significant changes are made we will endeavour to notify you.

In addition to this Notice, each service offered by us or our group of companies may have additional privacy provisions that are specific to the particular service. You will always be informed of these supplemental provisions at the time you provide your personal data.

### Using links to external sites

Please remember that when you use a link to go from our website to another website, our Privacy Notice no longer applies. Your browsing and interaction on any other website or your dealings with any other third party service provider, is subject to that website’s or third party service provider’s own rules and notices/policies. We do not monitor, control, or endorse the information collection or privacy practices of any third parties. This Notice applies solely to Information collected by us through our website or services and does not apply to these third party websites and third party service providers.

## About us

### Our contact details

If you have any questions about this Privacy Notice you can contact us in the following ways:

**Write to us:** Data Protection Officer, Haymarket Media Group, Bridge House, 69 London Road, Twickenham TW1 3SP.  
**Call us:** 020 8267 5000 (and ask for the Data Protection Officer)  
**Email our Data Protection Officer:** [data.protection@haymarket.com](mailto:data.protection@haymarket.com)

Haymarket Media Group’s registered office is Bridge House, 69 London Road, Twickenham, TW1 3SP.  
Registered in England and Wales under the company number: 00267189.  
VAT registration number is GB232584272.  
ICO registration number is: ZA445905.

### Our brands

#### Haymarket Automotive brands

#### Haymarket Business Media brands

Please be aware our brands based overseas will be subject to different Privacy Notices.

## Collection of your personal data

### Personal data you provide directly to us

We collect personal data from you when you enquire about or request a product or service directly from us. For example you will provide personal data to us when you;

  * register on one of our websites
  * join online forums
  * subscribe to a magazine
  * apply for a job
  * sign up for a digital product or service
  * register to attend a conference, an award or forum event
  * request a newsletter/bulletin
  * enter a competition or prize draw

The information we routinely collect will include your contact details (e.g. name, email address, phone number and postal address). We will also collect specific information where relevant for a particular service. For example, you would provide your car registration number if requesting a vehicle valuation or you may choose to upload your CV when using one of our job sites.

When you register to attend one of our events, we may also collect details about your dietary and accessibility requirements. We only collect this information with your explicit consent and will only use it for the purposes of your attendance at the event.

To learn more please see How we use your personal data.

### When you visit our websites

When you visit one of our websites for the first time, you will receive a “pop-up” notice informing you that we use Cookies. Some personal data (for example a unique identifier, your IP address and geographical location) will be collected through our and our technology partners’ use of cookies and similar technologies. To learn more please see our Cookie Notice.

### From other organisations or publicly available sources

We sometimes combine information we have collected from our websites or other sources, with information received from other organisations. This is used to:

  * verify the personal data we hold for you (e.g. to check your postal address is correct)
  * enhance the content and relevance of the advertising we provide to you. To learn more please see Personalisation of marketing & website content and our Cookie Notice.

We may also research publicly available sources (e.g. websites and LinkedIn) and use external suppliers, to identify business contacts who are likely to be interested in the products and services we have to offer. We will only collect the minimal amount of information required for this purpose (e.g. name, job title, company and contact details) and when we contact you we will always provide you with an easy way to object to us continuing to retain your personal data.

## The lawful bases we rely on

Under the GDPR there are six lawful bases under which organisations can collect, use and store personal data. We have identified four which we rely upon for our business activities: Consent, Contractual, Legitimate Interests and Legal Obligation.

Contractual – in many circumstances we rely on the lawful basis of “performance of a contract”, this enables us to respond to you when you express an interest in our products and services and to fulfil any requests. To learn more please see Fulfilment of a service.

Consent – in some circumstances we rely on your specific consent, whereby you actively agree and “opt-in”. We will always make it clear how you can withdraw you consent at any time. To learn more please see How to stop marketing communications.

Legal Obligation – there will be circumstances under which we are legally obliged to hold your personal data or required to disclose it to a third party by law.

Legitimate Interests – for some of our activities we rely on our legitimate business interests to collect and use your personal data. In such cases, we have balanced our interests with yours and do not believe these activities will have a negative impact on your privacy rights and freedoms. We specifically rely on Legitimate Interests to:

  * manage specific aspects of our events. To learn more please see Conference events, Award events and Forum events
  * send you marketing communications about our products and services. To learn more please see Marketing communications
  * send you marketing communications related to other companies’ products and services (in a business-to-business context). To learn more please see Marketing communications
  * personalise the marketing content we provide you. To learn more please see Personalisation of marketing & website content
  * share your contact details with a named sponsor, when you access specific sponsored content. To learn more please see Sponsored content
  * undertake business sales and advertising activities
  * share your CV with recruitment agencies (at your request) when you sign up for our job seeking services
  * research publicly available business contact details. To learn more please see Collection of your personal data and From other organisations or publicly available sources
  * customise the content you see on our websites. To learn more please see Personalisation of marketing & website content

You can always object to our marketing messages, please see How to stop receiving marketing communications.

If you wish to object to our reliance on Legitimate Interests for any other purpose please use Our contact details.

## How we use your personal data

### Fulfilment of a service

We will use your personal data for the purposes of fulfilling a product or service you have requested, which includes:

  * Responding to your enquiries about our products and services
  * Fulfilling your requests and delivery of a product or service. For example when you: 
    * subscribe to a magazine
    * register to attend an event
    * register to access online content
    * register to access site functionality
    * apply for a job
  * Administering your account
  * Sending you specific service or transactional communications about a product or service
  * Fulfilling prize draws and competitions
  * Delivering customer services

We use essential and functional cookies to ensure our websites function properly. To learn more please see our Cookie Notice.

### Live events

Some of our brands will organise live events aimed at delivering the latest information, insight and opinions from a wide range of industry sectors.

We will use the personal details you provide us when you register to attend an event so we know who’s attending and to allow access. If you are making a group booking or booking on someone’s behalf, please ensure you have their permission to share their name and contact details with us.

Photographs and video footage may be taken at our events and used in post-event publicity or future promotional material. If you don’t want to be captured in any photos or video footage, please let the photographer know on the day of the event. You can also [email us](mailto:live.eventsteam@haymarket.com?subject=Conference%20Event%20Privacy%20Query) if you believe you have been included in a photograph or video footage and object to it being used for post-event publicity or future promotional material.

For some of our events, you may be asked for your badge to be scanned by our seminar hosts, sponsors and exhibitors. By doing so, you are agreeing for the basic contact details you provided us during your registration to attend this event, to be shared with them. They will use this information to contact you in future for their direct marketing purposes. Further privacy notices will be displayed on the day of the event to remind you of this activity. If you do not wish for your details to be shared in this way, then please feel free to object to your badge from being scanned.

We will sometimes provide a formal meal where delegates are seated and receive table service. You are given the opportunity to inform us of any dietary requirements during the registration process. We only use this information for the purpose of your attendance at the event. To ensure we’re able to meet these requirements, we have to share this information with venues so you receive your dietary choice.

For some our events, the content is spread out over a few days and some delegates are provided with accommodation at venues hosting the event. To ensure a seamless professional service, we share personal details with venues to ensure rooms are booked under their name, and to enable easy check-in.

You may voluntarily inform us of specific accessibility requirements that help us ensure the service we provide you is specific to your needs. We only use this information for the purpose of your attendance at the event, and share it with venues hosting the event to help meet these requirements (e.g. table plans, specific accommodation).

We will also share the delegate list with the venue for fire regulation and safety purposes.

Please find below further information about how your personal details will be used when you register to attend one of our conferences, awards or forum events.

#### Conference events

These events are a chance for delegates and other visitors to meet, learn and discuss the latest topics and trends with other attendees and industry service suppliers.

We will share your details (name, job title and company name ONLY) with events sponsors and speakers, to help them prepare for networking opportunities and to ensure that any content and activity on the day is tailored specifically to the audience attending. If you would prefer us not to do this please [email us](mailto:live.eventsteam@haymarket.com).

#### Award events

These events are a chance to celebrate the achievements of both our clients and customers, which will involve the disclosure of some personal information.

Your details (name, job title and company name) will be shared with other attendees, including award sponsors, within an award brochure, event guide, table plan and screen presentation. Please [email us](mailto:live.eventsteam@haymarket.com?subject=Awards%20Event%20Privacy%20Query) if you would prefer your name not to appear.

#### Forum events

These events are specifically designed to invite delegates to tailored supplier meetings and to network with like-minded people. We believe it is in everyone’s interests for business contact details to be shared between delegates and suppliers. We will inform you about who the service suppliers are during the registration stage and when organising tailored supplier meetings.

If you have any queries or concerns please [email us](mailto:live.eventsteam@haymarket.com).

### Sponsored content

Our Haymarket Business Media brands often provide sponsored content, such as webinars, expert reports, whitepapers, surveys or events. Before being able to access any content, we ask that you create an free online account first. We collect basic work contact details and other information about your company and job role.

When accessing specific content that has been sponsored by another organisation, we will also ask you to complete a short form requesting your permission to share your details with the sponsor. We will share basic work contact details and some of the other information you provided when you created your account, or collected subsequently when accessing the specific content. We will always provide a link to the sponsor’s full privacy notice so you are fully aware of how they will process your personal data.

Sharing your details with the content sponsor is always your choice and you will always be provided with a clear opportunity to indicate if you would prefer us not to share this information.

### Job seeking service

Some of our Haymarket Business Media brands provide job seeking services that allow you to apply for jobs, receive job alerts and other job related emails, upload your CV, and share your details with recruiters via our searchable CV database. Your CV will only be included in our CV database with your permission. We ask for your permission when you upload your CV while applying for a specific job or creating an online account. You can subsequently choose to be removed from our CV database at anytime by changing your permission settings in your account area, or by [emailing us](mailto:onlinesupport@haymarket.com) directly.

If you apply for a job, your details will be shared with the recruiter promoting the specific role. At your request we will share your CV with Top CV so they contact you about receiving a free CV review.

### Marketing communications

When we collect your personal data we will include a specific notice to inform you and give you choices about future direct marketing communications from us.

We will only send you direct marketing communications when you have either:

  * provided your consent (e.g. ticked a box or clicked a “button” to submit a form)
  * where we believe we can demonstrate a legitimate business interest and have balanced this with your interests and privacy.

It is always your choice and you can stop receiving direct marketing communications from us at any time. We will provide a clear and easy way to do this on any communication you receive. To learn more please see How to stop marketing communications.

For electronic marketing communications (via email, sms and phone) we adhere to the rules of the Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations (PECR).

### Personalised marketing & website content

We want to ensure our marketing communications are of interest to you. We therefore use the information we know about you to tailor our messages to be more relevant. We will use details such as your gender, age, geographical location, previous transactional history, website usage, and your interactions with our marketing content to try and do this. Please also see our Cookie Notice. You have the right to object, but this will mean we will be unable to send your marketing communications in future, as we do not wish to send irrelevant messages to you. To learn more please see How to stop marketing communications.

We believe website content is more interesting to you when it is relevant. We provide tailored recommendations and advertisements to customise the content that you see on our websites. To do this, we use cookies and similar technologies through various technology partners to help us understand how you interact with our websites (e.g. the content you viewed on a previous visit or aggregated website performance analytics). To learn more please see our Cookie Notice.

## How to stop receiving marketing communications

We don’t want to send you marketing communications if you do not want to receive them. You can stop receiving these messages from us at anytime.

We have a diverse range of brands in our Haymarket Automotive, and Haymarket Business Media divisions, which you may not realise are all published by Haymarket Media Group. You may therefore wish to be selective and just stop receiving marketing communications from one brand rather than from them all.

**Emails** : There will always be an unsubscribe link on any marketing email you receive from us. Some of our brands (where relevant) provide a level of granularity to the types of emails you can unsubscribe from.  
**Post** : We will inform you in any postal communication how you can stop receiving direct mail in future.  
**Phone** : If you receive a marketing call from us, please let the call operator know if you don’t want to receive calls again.  
**SMS** : Please text “STOP” to any message received.

If you wish to stop ALL marketing communications from Haymarket Media Group please click the button below (remember this will stop all marketing communications from all of our brands).  

If you wish to contact us directly about marketing communications you are receiving, please use one of the contact details below:  
**Write to us** : Data Protection Officer, Haymarket Media Group, Bridge House, 69 London Road, Twickenham TW1 3SP  
**Call us** : 020 8267 5000 (and ask for the Data Protection Officer)  
**Email our Data Protection Officer** : [data.protection@haymarket.com](mailto:data.protection@haymarket.com)

## Sharing your personal data

We may share your personal data with other organisations, as specifically approved by you or under the circumstances described below.

### Our events

We may share limited personal data about you with event sponsors, other delegates and venues. To learn more please see:

  * Award events
  * Conference events
  * Forum events

We will always make it clear and provide you with choices if another organisation wishes to use your personal data for their own marketing purposes.

### Our service suppliers

We use a number of companies to help us in providing a professional service to our customers. For example, a subscription fulfilment bureau, call centres and legal and professional services. These companies only act under strict contractual instruction from us. We limit the personal data we share with our suppliers to only those necessary to fulfil the specific service they provide to us. To learn more please see Fulfilment of a service

### Audit and verification

We may share your personal data with the auditing organisation, ABC (Audit Bureau of Circulations Ltd). This is only so ABC can verify aggregated statistics about circulation and usage of our products or review our policies, processes and procedures for compliance with relevant standards. To learn more please see [ABC’s Privacy Policy](http://www.abc.org.uk/privacy-policy).

### Legal Disclosure

We may need to disclose your personal data to comply with any legal obligation. These requests will be verified before we consider to share your details.

### Changes to our company

In the event we go through a business transition such as a merger or acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your personal data may be among the assets transferred.

## Social Media, message boards and chat

### Using social media sign-in

On some of our websites we enable you to sign in using a service like Twitter or Facebook.

We will inform you if we wish to access more than just basic account information during this process, so you can let us know you are happy to share these details with us.

We recommend you also check what permissions you enable in your social media profiles.

### Using message boards and chat

Any information which you choose to voluntarily post to message boards, chat rooms and other interactive forums, is by its very nature being made publicly available to other users who have access to that portion of a website or service. We would encourage you not to share your personal data and we are not responsible for any information you choose to provide or communicate in such forums. Any disclosures you make are at your own risk.

If you are having difficulty deleting or editing a post, please email: [data.protection@haymarket.com](mailto:data.protection@haymarket.com)

## Protecting children

All of our brands are aimed at adults and are not designed for use by children. However, we accept that on occasion children may visit our websites. Where we believe any of our brands may attract children under the age of 16, we will clearly provide information notices to try and deter children from providing their personal data.

We clearly stipulate that entry into any of our competitions is only available to over 18s. In exceptional circumstances we may lower this, but never lower than 16 and this will always be clearly stipulated in the terms and conditions for the specific competition.

We do not knowingly intend to send marketing communications to children.

We actively encourage all our staff, whenever they are implementing new promotions, offers or events to assess whether these might be attractive to children and if so, will ensure clear information is provided to try and deter children from providing their personal data.

If you are a parent or guardian and are concerned that we may be processing personal data related to your child, please use Our contact details.

## Your rights

Under data protection law you have a number of rights. These are aimed at giving you control about how your personal data is used by us.

To object to direct marketing, please see: How to stop marketing communications

To exercise any of your rights please use Our contact details.

If you are unhappy with the manner in which we have collected and are using your personal data please do not hesitate to contact us.

If you are concerned with the manner in which we have handled your personal data, you have the right to complain to a supervisory authority. In the UK this is the [Information Commissioner’s Office](https://ico.org.uk/).

### Access your personal data

You can request a copy of the personal data we may hold relating to you, and the purposes for which we are using it. This is known as a Subject Access Request. In responding to such a request we may ask for proof of your identity, to ensure we do not inadvertently send your personal data to another person. We will endeavour to respond to any such requests as soon as possible, but at least within one calendar month. Please use Our contact details.

### Amend your personal data

If you discover or believe the personal data we hold for you is out of date or incorrect please let us know and we will rectify this as soon as possible. Please use Our contact details.

### Delete your personal data

If you wish for your personal data to be deleted we will assess any such request on a case-by-case basis. We will respond to you as soon as possible, at least within one calendar month of receiving your request. Please use Our contact details.

## Keeping your data secure

### Where we store and process your personal data

Ensuring your personal data is kept and transferred securely is of the highest importance to us.

We hold your personal data on our secure systems, mainly based within the UK and the European Economic Area (EEA). Please also see How we keep your personal data secure. Where we employ service providers, we have appropriate agreements in place to ensure your personal data is protected.

Your personal data may be transferred to a country outside the European Economic Area (EEA). This may be required for the purposes of our staff based outside the EEA or where a supplier of a service is based outside the EEA. We will take all reasonable steps necessary to ensure your personal data is treated securely. This includes Model Contractual Arrangements as approved by the European Commission, and the EU-US Privacy Shield.

### How we keep your personal data secure

We are committed to protecting the security of the personal data we hold. We deploy appropriate technical and organisational measures to ensure your personal data is kept securely and to prevent any unauthorised access. We have robust procedures and features in place to prevent such unauthorised access.

We also require any parties to whom we transfer personal data to ensure they have appropriate security measures in place. Please also see Fulfilment of a service.

### How long do we keep your personal data

We hold personal data for a variety of different purposes and the length of time we keep your information for will vary depending on the products and services we are providing to you. We will only keep your personal data for a reasonable period of time and we base this on the purpose for which we are using it.

There will be circumstances in which we keep a strictly minimal amount of information about you, for example to ensure we can honour an objection to receiving direct marketing. We will also, in specific circumstances, be required to retain personal data for a longer period of time for contractual or legal reasons.

We have a detailed internal schedule for ensuring we do not hold your personal data for longer than we justifiably need it. To learn more please use Our contact details.

### Reporting security vulnerabilities

We are committed to the privacy, safety and security of our customers. If you discover a potential security vulnerability, we would ask you to please report it just to us in a responsible manner. Please email us at [data.protection@haymarket.com](mailto:data.protection@haymarket.com) and we will respond to you as soon as possible. This provides us with an opportunity to work with you and quickly address and resolve any issue. Publicly disclosing a potential vulnerability could put the wider community at risk, and therefore we encourage you to come to us first. We’ll keep you informed as we move forward with our investigations.

## Cookie Notice

The aim of our Cookie Notice is to provide you with a summary of the tracking technologies we use and how you can control what is set and when. We keep our Cookie Notice under regular review to best reflect the technology we use on our sites.

### Cookies and tracking technologies we use

Where Haymarket Media Group Ltd or its group companies talk about cookies and tracking technology on our websites (please see Our brands) we refer to the following:

#### Flash Cookies

A local shared object, sometimes called a “Flash cookie,” is a data file that can be created on your computer by the websites you visit. They are most often used to enhance your web-browsing experience. Adobe’s website provides details regarding [Flash Cookies](https://www.adobe.com/devnet/flashplayer/articles/privacy.html)

#### Web Beacons

To help us better manage content we employ web beacons in emails that we send to our subscribers. Web beacons are tiny graphics with a unique identifier and are used to track the online movements of internet users. Unlike cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, web beacons are embedded invisibly on websites. We use them in our HTML-based emails to learn which emails have been opened by recipients enabling us to gauge the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.

#### Pixels

A pixel refers to the code that is placed on your computer in order to trigger a cookie. We sometimes use this methodology to allow us to deliver more relevant messages to you e.g. to understand how you interact with our email marketing.

#### Log Files

We use log files to record events that occur on our websites. This may include, though not exclusively, the type, content or time of transaction made via your device. These audit trails allow us to analyse activities on our websites.

### How and why we use cookies and tracking technologies

#### Types of Cookies and how they are set

There are two types of cookies:

  1. “Session Cookies” – Stored temporarily in your computer’s memory while you are visiting a website and are deleted when you close your browser.
  2. “Persistent Cookies” – Stored for a set period on your computer and used to determine whether there has been any contact between us and your computer in the past.

There are two ways cookies set can be on our websites:

  1. “1st Party Cookies” – cookies that are set by the website domain (or belonging to a sub domain) of the website.
  2. “3rd Party Cookies” – cookies that are set by another website domain. (e.g. by one of our main technology partners or by an external web services)

#### Cookies Classification

We are categorising cookies set on the site by ourselves and our main technology partners into the following categories:

**Category 1: Strictly necessary cookies**  
These cookies are essential, as they enable you to move around a website and use its features, such as accessing secure areas. Without these cookies, services you’ve asked for (such as access to secure areas) can’t be provided. These cookies don’t gather information about you that can be used for marketing or remembering where you’ve been on the internet.

**Category 2: Performance cookies**  
These cookies collect information about how you use a website, for example which pages you go to most often and if you get any error messages from certain pages. These cookies don’t gather information that identifies you. All information these cookies collect is anonymous and is only used to improve how our website works. These cookies are not used to target you with online advertising. Without these cookies we can’t learn how our website is performing and make relevant improvements that could better your browsing experience.

**Category 3: Functionality cookies**  
These cookies allow a website to remember choices you make (such as your user name, language or the region you’re in) and tailor the website to provide enhanced features and content for you. For instance, they can be used to remember log-in details, changes you’ve made to text size, font and other parts of pages that you can customise. They may also be used to provide services you’ve asked for such as watching a video or commenting on a blog. These cookies may be used to ensure that all our services and communications are relevant to you. The information these cookies collect cannot track your browsing activity on other websites. Without these cookies, a website cannot remember choices you’ve previously made or personalise your browsing experience.

**Category 4: Targeting and advertising cookies**  
We use these to provide adverts on our sites that we believe are more relevant to you. Without these cookies, online adverts you encounter will be less relevant to you and your interests. We also enable some advertising partners to set cookies specifically to enable them to analyse advertising campaign performance.

#### Our main technology partners

We work directly with a number of technology partners to maintain and enhance our websites. We will update the following table when cookies are added or removed.

**Google DoubleClick**  
We use Google DoubleClick for the delivery and measurement of advertising campaigns.  

**Google AdWords**  
We use Google AdWords to promote our products and services through Google’s advertising opportunities.  

**Google Analytics**  
We use Google Analytics to provide insight into how visitors find and use our web pages so that we can evaluate and develop them. We also use Google Analytics to analyse how our audiences interact with our marketing content, for example what content is “clicked on”, so we can ensure we present relevant content which our audiences are interested in.  

**Data Hygge**  
We use Data Hygge to help us understand patterns in user behaviour so our Product and UX teams can create better user experiences. Data Hygge does this by deploying cookies that collect pseudonymised data points from interactions on our What Car? website.  

**Lotame**  
We use Lotame to allocate our audiences into segments based on their browsing behaviour so that we can serve relevant and interesting advertising to our users.  

**Facebook**  
We use Facebook to promote our products and services.  

**GroupM**  
We use GroupM to help personalise the advertising you see.  

**Outbrain**  
We use Outbrain for content recommendations.  

**Skimlinks**  
We use Skimlinks to help us attribute traffic.  

**Dax**  
We use Dax to customise the Radio advertising provided.  

#### External web services

We use a number of web services to display external content, e.g. YouTube. These could set cookies or track your activity anonymously – for full information you should read the privacy policies of these sites.

#### Our use of cookies on third party sites

We may set cookies on certain third party sites that we advertise on to identify you as having visited that site if you later visit our website, and will serve targeted advertising based on this information.

### Your control options

When you use any of our websites for the 1st time you will be notified about our use of cookies via a “pop up” banner. This is to inform you that cookies or similar technologies are deployed on your device. Some of these cookies or similar technologies may facilitate the processing of personal data. To learn more, please see Our main technology partners.

#### Managing your cookies

You can choose to disable your web browser’s ability to accept cookies. Please note that if you choose to do this, you may not be able to access or take advantage of many features of the service and some parts of the website may not work properly.

You can control how cookies are set within your browser settings. Each browser is different so check the ‘Help’ menu of your particular browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences, please see:

If you want to learn more about cookies, or how to control or delete them, you may also visit: [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) You may also wish to review the guidance provided by the Information Commissioner’s Office <https://ico.org.uk/for-the-public/online/cookies/>

#### Managing your preferences

**Do Not Track Signals**  
We currently do not respond to web browsers Do Not Track but will continue to review the Do Not Track concept and may adopt a standard once available. If we do so in the future, we will provide all relevant information in this policy.

**Online Advertising**  
For more information about online behavioural advertising please see:  
Advertising Standards Authority guide to [Online Behavioural Adverts](https://www.asa.org.uk/about-asa-and-cap/the-work-we-do/what-we-cover.html)  
Your Online Choices website, tips and advice about Online Behavioural Adverts and opting-out can be found in the [Your Ad Choices](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices).

### Contact us about Cookies

If you want to find out more or request information about our Cookie Notice use Our contact details

## Changes to our Privacy Notice

If we decide to change our privacy notice we will post the changes here.

July 2018: Updated to include additional technology partners who deploy cookies on our websites, with links to further information and controls.

October 2018: Removed other companies within the Haymarket Media Group. Updated the website and marketing personalisation section. Added email marketing as an example of how pixels are used, within the ‘Pixels’ section. Updated the Google Analytics tech supplier section to illustrate its use for personalising content.

March 2019: Added Data Hygge as a technology partner.
